bestguestpost.com 2018-08-22

# Best Guest Post

## Privacy Policy

Best Guest Post is committed to providing you with excellent online tech help services in Technology sector and also we strongly respect your right to privacy. We have developed this Privacy Statement to inform you about our practices to keep the customer's data safe and secured. Privacy is of great concern to most users, and is a critical part of an enjoyable and satisfactory user experience. We at Best Guest Post are acutely aware of and sensitive to the privacy concerns of our customers and other visitors who visit our web site. Best Guest Post don't do business with Minor. Best Guest Post follows these privacy principles both online and offline in the collection, use, security and sharing of customer information:

**NOTICE -** We collect personal information for our records. When we ask for your personal information, we will tell you why we need it and what we will do with it.

**CHOICE -** When we contact you for marketing purposes, we will let you know how to remove your name from future marketing efforts. 

**SECURITY -** We will use reasonable security measures to protect the personal information we receive from you. 

**SHARING -** We do not share customer details of any form with anybody. However, if required, we may share some specific information with our associated service providers only to deliver any service to you and during any such event we will inform you in advance to seek your approval. Also, we will require our authorized service providers to comply with all applicable legal requirements regarding the privacy of your information. 

As part of your interaction with Best Guest Post , we may collect personal information such as: Contact information, including name, mailing address, phone number and e-mail address. Purchase information, including credit card number, billing and/or shipping address. We may also collect demographic information, including age, personal interests and product preferences. 

We may request and/or collect personal information when you:  
1.Set up an account online.  
2.Schedule an appointment for services.  
3.Participate in a survey.  
4.Contact us with a question or concern  
. 5.Participate in other activities with Best Guest Post .  
6.Purchase products or services.
